everything-pr.com 2014-11-12

# Privacy Policy - Everything PR

_**Privacy Policy**_

We have created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to protect your privacy and to fully disclose what information we collect and how we use it. Please note your use of our site is also governed by the Terms and Conditions of use.

 **Information Collection and Dissemination**

You may visit this Web site without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. As you browse our Web site, the site collects log file, IP address of your computer, and other standard tracking data we use to evaluate site traffic and usage patterns. Such information is aggregated with tracking data from all site visitors.

Some portions of this Web site may require you to give us personally identifiable information such as your name, company, physical mailing address, e-mail address, telephone and fax numbers for, without limitation, registration for attendance at certain conferences and events; and subscriptions to our publications.

If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to our online sites, surveys or contest entries, any information provided in such communications may be collected as Personal Information.

If you elect to provide us Personal Information, we use it primarily to deliver the service you requested. Other uses of Personal Information are described elsewhere in this Policy. Your Personal Information is not shared with third parties in any way.

 **Information on Children**

As a business-to-business company, we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 18.

 **Cookies**

A “cookie” is a bit of data sent by a Web site through the browser to the computer of the user visiting the site, and enables the site to return the results the browser expects. Pamil Visions PR uses temporary, session-specific cookies to ensure visits to its Web site are smooth and customized for the visitor. Such cookies allow us to provide a visitor’s browser with information tailored to the visitor’s preferences and needs. If you do not want your browser to accept cookies, you can turn off the cookie acceptance option in the browser’s settings.

We use advertising companies to develop banner ads for our Web site. These ads may contain cookies. These companies collect cookies sent to your browser through the banner ads and we do not have control or access to this data.

 **Notification of Changes**

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Web site. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Web site. Please check back often to review the latest version of our Privacy Policy.

 **Your Acceptance of these Terms**

By using our Web sites, products or services, you signify your acceptance of the terms of this site – if not don’t visit the site.
